[Praise]
Jhala ka
and tell me
[Praise]
Hello friends, my name is Sachi and
I welcome you to your own YouTube channel Wealth.
Friends, as you
can see, I have added Aadi A
here, that is, licking, so if you
can see its volume, that volume is the
oldest, see any volume for a long time
and it is being seen today. If
we talk about last month, then
you can see that in the last month, you can see that in this big month, 130
subscribers, 18 crore, so
friends, before moving ahead in the video, let
me tell you that these are some videos which
I have done on my face,
like Indraprastha Gas, Ajeeb C
Restaurant, Company Report India, Varun
Beverages, Judge D Mart, Titan Industries and
Top Ten Penis, so if you want, you can
shrink it on my channel, so friends, you
can see, this nozzle net profit of the
company came out to be 1.5 inch, it was Kumar's 108, which
finally came out in quantity, which is
1945, which is from last year.  A 14 percent
increase was seen in the net profit.
After that, when the net profit was
advanced for the quarterly results, at that
time it was told that in order to
strengthen and strengthen our balance sheet, whenever an
opportunity arises, we will go for a sale.
After getting the approval, after that approval, they sold 1.8
crore equity shares which were of face value of
3 rupees to the ARTS company,
which if you say in total, is 3.6
percent stake
and Rs 2250 crore was sold today.
If we talk about it, after this year, just
one share of ICICI Bank remains, it comes out to be
21.9 percent in the silent general sense. Along with this, you can see
that the contribution of general insurance is the
highest in the consolidated profit of ICICI Bank. Out of nine
subsidiaries, this is the result friends,
due to which we got to see such a big
spark in the volume chart today.  Because
1.8 crore shares were sealed in the General Insurance market
by ICICI Bank. So friends, if
you haven't added this stock to your
portfolio yet and you are
interested in buying this stock, then
if we talk about it, you
can see that here the stock made a higher price,
then the current price was made, then if the
old price was already very high, then the price
made was above the old price,
so it made a lower price. You can see that the
old price had increased even more,
but this was the time when the
stimulus package was announced and the
market was
running at 9828, if you remember, and
after that, the price made can be
fitted here as an exception. This was a
day when the market was very
bad news because the expected price turned out to be as expected
in the market and a very huge
fall was seen in the information and Nifty
reached around 800, that is the
chart of that day, so look at this day on agriculture,
you can see it here.  From here it is again
going to the plate and after that it has again
made a log from here, so if you look
here, you can already see this side support line
in white color and along with it
you can see this green colored line, this is
its two medium moving average and today's
project is its power point and U&K
moving average which had turned sideways yesterday, it is
above that, which has provided very strong
support, both together have
provided its today's employment around 1270, so
from here now what is its target, what
targets can it achieve in one year, should we
invest in it or not,
further in this video we will see, first we will
mix its basic fundamentals and
in search we will check the target price, future
for class, see it and
after that decide a line level, for this talk
friends, before moving ahead in the video, let
me tell you that do
not forget to like and subscribe the video so that
we want to reach you with the latest videos like this, so
friends, if we talk about this company profile, then you
can see ICICI Lombard General,
second season, India's best private sector
non-life  Insurance means that we provide
insurance in turn on life like
travel insurance or any other
kind of thought insurance or any other
such person in whom life does
not improve, after that if we talk about the home sector then
finance comes out,
insurance is a large cap stock, if we
talk about the market place then its strength comes out
and after color then planet comes out 34,
talk about its tax value,
friends you can see that the current price is coming out
on intrinsic value, if we compare
return versus then the
return is seen to be much better here, if we talk about
limited then this
topic is so tractor here, it does
not deposit, then if we talk about this report then
Uber is not in the wards right now, so other
points are telling this and if we talk reflectively then there is no
side effect in this topic
because there
is no promoter placeholder in it and at any
time in which it does not make a straight line,
if we talk about soil of this,
friends then you can see that the P of the sector is coming out
22.24 and stock capital  It
came out to be 48.3. If we talk about the fourth pillar, then
1.7 of the sector and 10.00 of the stock,
talking about custom duty, friends, the sexy
seven per cent and migrating is
given here and now the price off side is 7.38, this is what
they say about it,
friends, if we talk about its detailed chart, then
you can see that
I have edited it, so
if we check the momentum from January 1, then in 6, it has
given a return of 15.81 percent in negative,
whereas Salman Aamir has
fallen less than 8.5 percent on social media, if we
talk about the time period of one year, then you can see that in this
program, friends, it is 11.20 percent in negative, whereas in ICICI
Lombard, we have given 90 percent
positive merit, so
if there is no tension of 3 years,
friends, you can see that only in the
meeting, there is 2% career, whereas here it is
not written 'IS A Romantic' because it has
not yet completed 360 in 3 years.  It
is less than 2 years, 9-10 minutes, Shiva, and if we
talk about hotness till now, then here we have
given this 96.45 percent, if we talk about friends'
fans, then you can see that a
charge of Rs. 400 has been levied for 17, 18, 19, 20 minutes, if
you say that last time I had said that
this is less than 3 years, Chakli, in 2017
it was listed here in September, so
when the number of 2020 will come, then it will be 1, 2, 3 years from here, so
here this entire
year, in 2017 it was not listed here,
so
you did not get to see its data in the return chart here,
but if we talk about its total revenue,
then you can see that we are continuously
seeing a boom here,
which is also a very good thing since August, but if we
talk about the mind, then here you can see that it has
increased from one crore to 861 to 1049 and
here the meeting of 2020 is not less, read and written right
now  I already told you the news
that
around 1100 offices are going to be opened or something like that, a total of 14
percent work was seen here, there was a rise here since last year
and if we
talk about Arvind's share, then here you can see that
Anil's share is also increasing year after year,
so this data is coming out quite good.
After that, if we talk about its income statement, then
you can see that friends, as far as
revenue is concerned, we have seen less growth here than the
average industry growth which is 19.39 percent.
In the last 5 years, 14.6 percent has been seen, so there is a
decrease of 5 percent here.
If we talk about market share, in 5 years, in
this way the market share has increased from 1.9
to 3.7 percent, which is a very good thing.
And if we talk about its net income,
friends, then in 5 years it has given an average income of
15.7 percent,
whereas the average growth of the industry has come out to be
3.5 inches from here you can see
just the face of the computer click 15.07
is quite high, it is better, so this total
silence we can do much better, this
token was coming out friends, tree
and voting pattern, you
can see all this, promoter holding is coming out was
55.06 percent here
Australia three point something print,
so you know how much the wards have become
and it has been shown, if we talk about it then
sandwich point 10.47 notification 7.57 at 23.31 and
Aadarsh ​​2.7, so if we talk about airplane promoter holding,
as I told you,
zero is not at all a proper place should be shown
and if we talk about mutual funds, then I have
my skin interest in it in Quite Different Mutual Funds and if we talk about face, then I have invested
553 in Defense Can Invest and if we
talk about portal which is called, then
easily Bank Limited is coming out which
I had told you earlier and if we
talk about public shoulder, then
mutual funds through various schemes in it
2.1  If we talk about the
change in its share holding pattern
between December 2019 and March 2020, then you can see that there is a
slight decrease in it
and we will mark a slight decrease
and 1 minute amount is
that mutual funds and if we are seeing it getting integrated within IS, then
here we can say that it has just
shifted from one segment to another, so
friends, if we talk about its price forecast, then
you can see
this is till June 2021 and here you can see that
if it goes to the media then
I can see a profit of 7.8 percent here
from the current price which is
coming out to be 20.15 and in this, if it
goes to the side, we can see a water of 35
which
can give a return of 31 percent less in the negative and if it is
seen going to the high side then
we should see a price of 1574  We can get it, which at the
current price
can give us a positive return of 23.92 percent. As you
will see, friends, we have not given focus to Renu here, so
we will see the
podcast of Arvind Price share ourselves and if we
talk about Anil Price's forecast, then you
can see that the running speculated growth
GPS is on the 21.28 initial,
which if we talk about the last step of the gas, it was coming out at
19.00, so as per the last
two-three years, the growth in
Anil's share will be more this year, it is
said and right now the share price of Ajwain is
around 46.27, which is
intimate with the quality 1.2 percent,
so we can see the effect on doing 31.8 next year,
if it goes low then it can be seen at
45.57 and if it goes high then it can be
seen at 36.47, so friends,
as seen in the case above also, it is the last
step share and this is General
Insurance in that chapter.
Insurance is the largest in India and we saw that
its zone return chart
compared to other stocks, so in every time frame it has given
us higher returns. If we
talk about wedding material finance, then it is
quite good. If we
talk about Ravindra's net income
or Arvind Parishad, we have seen it increasing continuously in the last 4 years.
Along with this, if we talk about computer holding, then
it also turned out to be very good.
Along with this, when we looked at Prakash,
I saw that if it is medium size, if
it goes to Prakash of ticket, then its
maximum will go around 3875, which is currently
above travel. If we look at this idea, then
we can see it going to the level around zero. So as of now,
as can be
seen in the level,
here the fiber is already at the support level,
so if you want, you can take cream in it within this support level.
If it
supports them and falls, then here you will be
seeing that its solution is the moving
average and 50 day moving average.  It is
seen crossing here, so at this
level around 1228 12345 preparation
falls again, if you do it then you
can make a mark here or sometimes
bad news comes and we see even more
fall, so
after this you can see the support level of powder,
Lavender 65, so at this
level you can make a dam here, so
if I write it for you, first it will come out at
1270, which is there, you can buy art,
if you are still in Australia and are interested in it, then secondly it will
come out at
around 1234 and after that it will come out at
around 1160, so if you want, you can come to Villagers and
share this, you can see it, then you
can do it inside it and at the same time
friends, I would like to tell you that this is a
way of sharing where whenever there is a fall in the hard disk, you should
point, so right now, as
you were seeing a fall, hence that
level has been reached, so you can remind here
as I told you that you can do it,
then when  Also, there is a decline in the next picture
after 2 months or
after 1 month from here, so you can again make small
changes in it and whenever you see a decline,
you can gradually keep increasing your stock in it and
grow your portfolio and
with this we end the video, thank you bye,
take care.